So hello friends, look today, see the market
sentiment, that is, the market has given a
negative closing today, so
how can you people trade in the stock market on
Monday, some stock market news which can be
useful for you people, you
can watch the full video till end, see, look at the
market, see Nifty, today it has not given 100%, that is,
100 points and it has also given a 400 point
drop, Bank Nifty has fallen more and is
close to 1 and Nifty IT has
fallen by 1%, see the
selling on 17th, see there was selling of 33000 crores, that
means he is not even buying right now, see on
16th also there was 4000-43000
crores, see what is the selling, that means the
foreign investors are selling in our market right now, they are
buying a little bit from the stock, let me show you some stock market
news, the first
news, see, is Bharat
Electronics Limited, see its bill, that
means the price is going up by 81,
see  Today the market has given a downward
closing, that is, an upward move,
so look at this, there is some news which I will
show you guys, see Motilal and
Sapal which is a brokerage company, that is, a broker, have
given a growth of 30,
look at the stock, that is, they have given a target of around 360,
see right now, that means the market
price is 80 and the target given is 360, that
means it is close to 30, that is, what has been expected, that
means if the brokers have given it, then it
means if the market goes, that is, it will go sideways, it is nothing,
but whatever has been given right now,
it will definitely move on Monday, so you
guys should keep the stock on the rudder, in 9:1 miters, the stock
can give a good move on Monday,
look at the bell and a news has come, look at
Macrotech Developers Limited, see today
after the news came in the stock, it has given a move of 4,
see at 50, that is, it has given a
closing in 50-50 point offer, and if you look at its news, then let me
show you the news, the
news is about Kotak Security, that is  The
broker of Int Equity which is Kotak Security,
Kotak Institutional Equities, had
given a buy rating for buying, after that see, the
market had given a move at 6, which means a
little at 2, which means settlement happened by the end of the market, so
you
can see the stop on the radar right now, that is,
look at Macrotech Developers, one stock, ICCI
Lord, today it has given an upside move at 2, so the reason
behind this is that
you people have seen a lot of news, so
see, after the result of its sector,
see, it has made a profit of 68, which
means it has made a
profit of 726 crores, the margin
also fell due to which the
profit has also been quite good, so ICCI
Ltd, which means this is a very good and important stock, it will
give a very good move, see the news that came, that is,
after the market ended, see the news came
at 541, so look at the market, it gave a move, which
means someone, someone from the company came to know about it, quite a lot, which
means the result came.  It can,
therefore, see, it has given a move, so see,
big investors do the same, so the
IC A stock, you guys should
definitely keep it on the radar at 9:1, meaning it can give a move, so
I will not
say to buy it, it can give a good move,
you guys can keep the stock on the radar, see and there is a
news that has come, Aadhar Housing Finance
Limited, see the stock, it has
not given a good move, meaning it has given a closing in the positive,
see the market has gone down, even
after that, see the stock is
holding a very good price today, it has
not given a closing in the negative, so see the
news of this, see, Citi Institution
which is a booker, see, it has given a buy
rating to Aadhar Housing Finance stock,
see, CK means it can go upside at 42,
so see the stock,
after what Sunny means Bokej has covered,
see, the stock can give a move, so
watch the stock, you should keep the stock on the radar after 9 o'clock, it has
given a good move, see, the
target given is 565, so
you guys should watch the stock on the radar  You can
see one stock which is quite good is
Mahindra Tech Mahi, so see today the market means the
stock is very good for buying,
you can buy it, so you will say see it
closed in negative, then
why are you ready to buy, so see there is
a news about it, so I will show you the news, so
you can see its
price,
1697, so see the news of the stock, see its
quarter
result came out, after that see at 93, that means it has made a
profit, which is on year on year basis, it has
made a profit of Rs 83 crore, that
means see the month of December 24 ended,
after that see the quarter result
came out, see in the result its profit is Rs 93 crore, that
means you understand what is the profit at 93, it has
doubled on year basis,
its profit has doubled in one year, so it
means the stock will go up like a rocket, so right now
you people can put the stock on the buying
side, that is, I will not say for buying, the
stock means news  But
after the profit it has made, see, big
investors can invest in it,
so you can keep Tech Mahindra stock on your
radar. And look at the
result of the Popo Zopo sector, after that see, the
profit it made was net profit at 24 at
24.5, so YoYo means
its net profit is 33,394 crores,
so look, after that see, the stock has
said to give dividend, which is equity share at ₹6, that is,
dividend, so
if you have a stock, its price is
₹5000000, then by doing ₹
6 on each stock, then
now it will give dividend, so see, this stock has
made profit and see, it is also
giving dividend, so there will be momentum in the stock,
so keep the stock on your radar, that is, I am
saying tomorrow,
keeping the stock on the radar on Monday can give a very good move.